Guide to the Kevin Killian and Dodie Bellamy Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Kevin Killian and Dodie Bellamy papers
1948-2015
YCAL MSS 1090
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
101.62
86 boxes
Killian, Kevin
Bellamy, Dodie
Arrangement
Organized into eight series: I. Correspondence, 1973-2015. II. Writings, 1952-2014. III. Professional Papers, 1941, 1979-2015. IV. Research Files, 1977-2009. V. Personal Papers, 1948, 1965-2005. VI. Photographs, 1965-2012. VII. Audiovisual Materials, 1977-2012. VIII. Electronic Media, 1991-2008.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 83-85 (audiovisual materials): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Box 86 (digital media): Restricted fragile material. Access copies of digital files may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from Granary Books on the Edwin J. Beinecke Book Fund, 2015.
Kevin Killian
Kevin Killian (b. 1952) is an American poet, writer, editor, and playwright. Killian and co-editor Peter Gizzi won the American Book Award for poetry in 2009 for My Vocabulary Did This to Me: The Collected Poetry of Jack Spicer (Middletown, Conn.: Wesleyan University Press, 2008). He is a co-founder of the Poets Theater performance group in San Francisco. Killian is married to Dodie Bellamy.
Dodie Bellamy
Dodie Bellamy is an American novelist, writer, journalist, and editor. Her work is associated with the New Narrative literary movement. Bellamy is married to Kevin Killian.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of correspondence, writings, professional papers, research files, personal papers, photographs, audiovisual materials, and electronic media documenting the lives and work of Kevin Killian and Dodie Bellamy. The correspondence documents their personal, professional, and family networks and includes writers, poets, and collaborators. Writings include published and unpublished works by both Killian and Bellamy. Professional papers include essays, talks, and other papers documenting their work and careers. Research files document Bellamy's research on Sam D'Allesandro for Real: The Letters of Mina Harker and Sam D'Allesandro (Hoboken, N.J.: Talisman House, 1994), and Killian's research on Jack Spicer for My Vocabulary Did This to Me: The Collected Poetry of Jack Spicer, which he co-edited with Peter Gizzi. Personal papers include juvenilia, schoolwork, reviews, flyers, teaching materials, memorabilia, papers relating to Poets Theater, and other papers. Photographs include 8 x 10 prints, in both color and black and white, which mostly consist of portraits of Bellamy, Killian, and many other individuals. Photographs also include a series of photographs taken by Kevin Killian titled "Tagged," as well as general photographs of events and performances. Audiovisual materials include interviews regarding Jack Spicer, additional interviews, music, and other recordings. Electronic media includes audio recordings, research materials, digital photographs, and commercially-produced media.
American literature -- 20th Century; American literature -- 21st century; American poetry -- 20th Century; American poetry -- 21st century; Authors, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Authors, American -- 21st century -- Archives; Gay authors; Poets, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Poets, American -- 21st century -- Archives; Audiovisual materials; Born digital; Photographs; Authors -- United States -- 20th Century; Authors -- United States -- 21st century; Poets -- United States -- 20th Century; Poets -- United States -- 21st century; LGBTQ resource; Bellamy, Dodie; D'Allesandro, Sam; Gizzi, Peter, 1959-; Killian, Kevin; Spicer, Jack
- Correspondence, 1973-2015; Series I; 23.25; 25 boxes
  Arrangement
  Correspondence is organized into two groups. The first is arranged and listed alphabetically by correspondent. The second is arranged in several roughly alphabetical groupings but has not been sorted into a single sequence.
  - Alphabetical correspondence
    - Abbott, Alyssa, 1996-2005, undated (Box 1)
    - Abbott, Steve, 1983-1993, undated (Box 1)
    - Abelson, Alex, 2007, undated (Box 1)
    - Able Building Maintenance Company, 1988 October 11 (Box 1)
    - Acker, Kathy, undated (Box 1)
    - Ackerman, Gerald, 1993 (Box 1)
    - Adair, Gilbert, 1987, undated (Box 1)
    - Adams, Bobby Neal, undated (Box 1)
    - Adley, Rupert, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Adnan, Etel, 2002, undated (Box 1)
    - Agamben, Giorgio, 1985 May 22 (Box 1)
    - Aguilar, Ryan, undated (Box 1)
    - Aikin, Rhonda, 1988 November 04 (Box 1)
    - Albiach, Anne-Marie, 1998, undated (Box 1)
    - Albon, George, 1992-1998, undated; 2 (Box 1)
    - Aldan, Daisy, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Alden, Todd, 1993–1996 (Box 1)
    - Alexander, Charles, 1990–1997 (Box 1)
    - Alexander, Christopher, 1998-2004, undated (Box 1)
    - Alexander, Paul, 2007 December 11 (Box 1)
    - Alexander, Will, 2007 (Box 1)
    - Allen, Don, 1983-2004, undated (Box 1)
    - Donald Allen/Charles Olson MS, undated (Box 1)
    - Allen, Erin, 2008, undated (Box 1)
    - Allen, Parker Zane, undated (Box 1)
    - Allende, Isabel, 1998 July 23 (Box 1)
    - Allison, Dorothy, 1992-1994, undated (Box 1)
    - Alvarez, Darrell-Lynn, 1992-1998, undated (Box 1)
    - Alvi, Tariq, 2005-2014, undated; 2 (Box 1)
    - Alyson Books, 2009 June 15 (Box 1)
    - Alziati, Ricardo, 2013 November (Box 1)
    - Ameen, Mark, 1987-1989, undated (Box 1)
    - Amnasan, Michael, 1985-1986, undated; 2 (Box 1)
    - Anderson, Beth, 1994, undated (Box 1)
    - Andrews, Bruce, 1989-1991, undated (Box 1)
    - Angeline, Mary, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Angelou, Maya, undated (Box 1)
    - Apps, Stan, 2004, undated (Box 1)
    - Arcangelini, Michael, 2012 (Box 1)
    - Arensburg, Paul, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Argento, Dario, undated; 3 (Box 1)
    - Arkane, Jhonnie, 1990, undated (Box 1)
    - Armantrout, Rae, 1985-1990, undated (Box 1)
    - Arnone, Matthew, 2004 (Box 1)
    - Arobateau, Red Jordan, 1995-2005, undated (Box 1)
    - Aronson, Bill, 1987-1989, undated (Box 1)
    - Aronson, Mrs. Norman, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Artforum, 2014, undated (Box 1)
    - Arthur, Marc, 2007, undated (Box 1)
    - Ashbery, John, 2001, undated (Box 1)
    - Atlas, Charles, 2003 (Box 1)
    - Atkins, Tim, 1997, undated (Box 1)
    - August, Avery, undated (Box 1)
    - Auster, Paul, 1996 May 07 (Box 2)
    - Austin, Rodney O'Neal, 1993, undated (Box 2)
    - Autographs of the Stars, 1958-1989, undated (Box 2)
    - Avison, Margaret, 2004 November 20 (Box 2)
    - Azar, C., 1995, undated (Box 2)
    - Bachand, Therese, 2005, undated (Box 2)
    - Bachardy, Don, 2001 March 06 (Box 2)
    - Bacher, Lutz, 1986-1995, undated (Box 2)
    - Baham, Leon, 2011 (Box 2)
    - Baily, Bart, 2010–2012 (Box 2)
    - Baker, James Robert, 2000 October (Box 2)
    - Baker, Stephanie, undated (Box 2)
    - Ballard, Micah, 2006-2007, undated (Box 2)
    - Banks, Eric, 2003, undated (Box 2)
    - Baratier, David, undated (Box 2)
    - Barrymore, Drew, undated (Box 2)
    - Baron, Todd, 1987–1991 (Box 2)
    - Barone, Dennis, 1987-1988, undated (Box 2)
    - Barua, Dibakar, 1983 December 12 (Box 2)
    - Basinski, Michael, 1992-2001, undated (Box 2)
    - Beachy, Stephen, 1993-1994, undated (Box 2)
    - Beckett, Tom, 1986-1998, undated (Box 2)
    - Bedoya, Roberto, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Beeston, Rob, 2007, undated (Box 2)
    - Bellamy, Dodie, circa 1984 (Box 2)
    - Bellamy, Winifred, 2002-2007, undated (Box 2)
    - Belt, Mike, 1986 (Box 2)
    - Benderson, Bruce, 1990-1991, undated; 2 (Box 2)
    - Benka, Jen, 2005 November 03 (Box 2)
    - Bennett, Catherine, 1992 (Box 2)
    - Bennett, Guy, 1997 (Box 2)
    - Benning, Sadie, undated (Box 2)
    - Benson, Steve, 1985-1995, undated (Box 2)
    - Bentley, Scott, 1986-1998, undated (Box 2)
    - Bergman, David, 1997-1998, undated (Box 2)
    - Bergvall, Caroline, 1997, undated (Box 2)
    - Berkson, Bill, 1990-1998, undated; 2 (Box 2)
    - Berman, Tosh, 1991-1997, undated (Box 2)
    - Bernheimer, Alan, 1999, undated (Box 2)
    - Bernstein, Charles, 1993, undated (Box 2)
    - Bernstein, Lisa, 1987-1988, undated (Box 2)
    - Berrigan, Anselm, 1995, undated (Box 2)
    - Berrigan Brothers, undated (Box 2)
    - Berrigan, Edmund, undated (Box 2)
    - Bertholf, Robert J., 1986-1996, undated (Box 2)
    - Bettridge, Joel, 2004, undated (Box 2)
    - Between C and D, undated (Box 2)
    - Bianchi, Ray, undated (Box 2)
    - Black, Star, 1996, undated (Box 2)
    - Black, Terence, 1967-1978, undated (Box 2)
    - Blake, Nayland, 1991-1996, undated (Box 2)
    - Blanchfield, Brian and John Myers, 2013-2014, undated (Box 2)
    - Blanchfield, Brian, undated (Box 2)
    - Blaser, Robin, 1984-1985, undated (Box 2)
    - Blatty, William Peter, undated (Box 2)
    - Bliss, Anthony, 2003 (Box 2)
    - Blumenreich, Julia, 1987-1991, undated (Box 2)
    - Boas, Nancy, 2014 (Box 2)
    - Bode, Walt, 1991 November 01 (Box 2)
    - Boland, Eavan, 1994 (Box 2)
    - Bondhus, Charlie, 2003 (Box 2)
    - Bonetti, David, 1992–2006 (Box 2)
    - Bongiovanni, Sylvia, undated (Box 2)
    - Boone, Bruce, 1986-1993, undated; 2 (Box 2)
    - Borges, Rob, undated (Box 2)
    - Borkhuis, Charles, 1996 May 21 (Box 2)
    - Bornstein, Erica, 1991, undated (Box 2)
    - Bouchard, Daniel, 1996-2004, undated (Box 2)
    - Bouldrey, Brian, 1994-1997, undated (Box 3)
    - Bowering, George, 1997-2006, undated (Box 3)
    - Boyer, Stephen, undated (Box 3)
      Separated Materials
      2 DVD-Rs removed for separate housing. See Box 86.
    - Boykoff, Jules, 2004-2005, undated (Box 3)
    - Brady, Taylor, 1999-2004, undated (Box 3)
    - Bradley, Jennifer, 1983-1985, undated (Box 3)
    - Braindrop, Lily, 1992 December 09 (Box 3)
    - Braithwaite, Lawrence, 1994-2006, undated; 3 (Box 3)
    - Bram, Christopher, 1989-1995, undated (Box 3)
    - Brazil, David, 2007 September 26 (Box 3)
    - Brennan, Sherry, 2000-2001, undated (Box 3)
    - Breskin, David, undated (Box 3)
    - Brett, Laurel, 1981, undated (Box 3)
    - Brice, Nathaniel, 1984-1985, undated (Box 3)
    - Bright, Susan, 1984-1999, undated (Box 3)
    - Brito, Manuel, 1990-1996, undated (Box 3)
    - Brock, Craig, 1993-1995, undated (Box 3)
    - Brod, Rachel, 2000 December 29 (Box 3)
    - Brolaski, Julian, 2006 July 25 (Box 3)
    - Bromige, David, 1992-1994, undated (Box 3)
    - Bronk, William, 1989–1999 (Box 3)
    - Brooks, Jason Napoli, undated (Box 3)
    - Brossard, Nicole, 2001 (Box 3)
    - Brossard, Olivier, undated (Box 3)
    - Broughton, James, 1983-1997, undated; 2 (Box 3)
    - Brown, Brandon, undated (Box 3)
    - Brown, Evangeline, 1984, undated (Box 3)
    - Brown, Lee Ann, 1989-1994, undated; 2 (Box 3)
    - Brown, Rebecca, 1994-1995, undated (Box 3)
    - Browne, Colin, 1988-1990, undated (Box 3)
    - Browne, Laynie, 1994 (Box 3)
    - Brun, Laura, undated (Box 3)
    - Bryce, Lesley, 1991–1992 (Box 3)
    - Bunker, Michele and Maggie Drury, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Burger, Mary, 1994-1997, undated (Box 3)
    - Burgher, Elijah, 2010–2011 (Box 3)
    - Burke, Carolyn, 1987-1996, undated; 2 (Box 3)
    - Burket, Cheryl, 1998, undated (Box 3)
    - Burkhart, Kathe, 1991-2004, undated (Box 3)
    - Burkhardt, Rick, undated (Box 3)
    - Burnham, Clint, 1998 (Box 3)
    - Burns, Avery E.D., 1992-1996, undated (Box 3)
    - Burns, Gerald, 1989-1994, undated (Box 3)
    - Burton, Hilde, 1994 May 31 (Box 3)
    - Butler, Judith, 1993, undated (Box 3)
    - Buuck, David, 1995-1997, undated (Box 3)
    - Byrne, Ted, 1995 June 30 (Box 3)
    - Byrum, John, 1994, undated (Box 3)
    - Cabri, Louis, 1990-1991, undated (Box 3)
    - Cage, Diana, 2004 (Box 3)
    - Cain, Sarah, 2005-2007, undated (Box 3)
    - Campbell, Marsha, 2001-2007, undated (Box 3)
    - Camerawork, 2009 (Box 3)
    - Canan, Janine, 1985–1986 (Box 3)
    - Canning, Richard, 1988-1991, undated (Box 3)
    - Carey, Tom, 1989-1990, undated; 2 (Box 3)
    - Carll, Steve, 1991-1992, undated (Box 3)
    - Carmell, Dan, 1993 (Box 3)
    - Carmey, William, 1985 July 14 (Box 3)
    - Carpenter, Meta, 1988 (Box 3)
    - Carr, Michael, 2004-2006, undated (Box 3)
    - Carroll, Jon, undated (Box 3)
    - Carson, Anne, 2000, undated (Box 3)
    - Cashorali, Peter, 1985–1986 (Box 4)
    - Caspar, Barbara, 2006 (Box 4)
    - Castle, Terry, 1996–2005 (Box 4)
    - Catherall, David, 2007 (Box 4)
    - CCA Stationary, undated (Box 4)
    - Cermak, Barbara, 1992, undated (Box 4)
    - Cermak, Carolyn, 1980 (Box 4)
    - Chadwick, Cydney, 1991 (Box 4)
    - Champagne, James, 2012 (Box 4)
    - Champion, Miles, 1997-1998, undated (Box 4)
    - Chapman, Lee, 1995 (Box 4)
    - Chavez, Anna, undated (Box 4)
    - Cherin, Josh, 1993-1995, undated; 2 (Box 4)
    - Chernoff, Maxine, 1987-1998, undated (Box 4)
    - Cherkovski, Neeli, 1985-1987, undated (Box 4)
    - Chester, Laura, 1985-1987, undated (Box 4)
    - Chick, Jack, undated (Box 4)
    - Child, Abigail, 1990-1996, undated (Box 4)
    - Chivers, Steve, 1984-1985, undated (Box 4)
    - Chin, Justin, undated (Box 4)
    - Chisholm, Dianne, undated (Box 4)
    - Chaung, Takming, 2013 March 06 (Box 4)
    - Cierzo, Thomas, 1996-2001, undated (Box 4)
    - Civin, Marcus, 2007 (Box 4)
    - Clark, Jeff, 2003, undated (Box 4)
    - Clarke, Cheryl, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Clark, Susan, 1999 (Box 4)
    - Clinger, Ken, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Clodfelter, Loretta, 2006 (Box 4)
    - Cobb, Allison, 1993-1998, undated (Box 4)
    - Cohen, Alicia, 1993-1999, undated (Box 4)
    - Cole, Norma, 1989-1992, undated (Box 4)
    - Cole, Peter, 1990–1992 (Box 4)
    - Collier, Anne, undated (Box 4)
    - Collins, Jack, 1985-1988, undated (Box 4)
    - Collom, Jack, 2003 December 09 (Box 4)
    - Conant, Jeff, 1992-2004, undated (Box 4)
    - Conner, Bruce, 1996 (Box 4)
    - Console, Cyrus, 2006, undated (Box 4)
    - Conway, Jeffrey, 1996-2007, undated (Box 4)
    - Cook, Crystal, undated (Box 4)
    - Coolidge, Clark, 1998 (Box 4)
    - Cooper, Dennis, 1984-2004, undated; 3 (Box 4)
    - Cope, Stephen, 1999, undated; 3 (Box 4)
    - Colquhoun, Ewan, 1995, undated (Box 4)
      Scope and Contents
      Identified by Kevin Killian and Dodie Belamy as "Japanese Guy"
    - Corber, Mitch, 1991-1997, undated (Box 4)
    - Corbett, William, 1985-1994, undated (Box 4)
    - Corder, Eileen, 1989 March 17 (Box 4)
    - Corman, Cid, undated (Box 4)
    - Corn, Alfred, 1989-1990, undated (Box 4)
    - Cory, Alex, 1995 April 15 (Box 4)
    - Cory, Jim, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Cotter, Patty, undated (Box 4)
    - Coultas, Brenda, 2001 March 15 (Box 4)
    - Courtney, Erin, 1995–1996 (Box 4)
    - Cowart, Claire, 1979-1994, undated (Box 4)
    - Cox, Sarah Anne, 1998, undated (Box 5)
    - Crane, Margaret, 1994, undated (Box 5)
    - Crawford, Lynn, 1994, undated (Box 5)
    - Creeley, Robert, 1993-1995, undated (Box 5)
    - Crippen, Phil, 2005-2007, undated (Box 5)
    - Cronenberg, David, undated (Box 5)
    - Croskey, Becky, 1983, undated (Box 5)
    - Crossing Press, 1988-1992, undated (Box 5)
    - Crouse, John, 1996, undated (Box 5)
    - Culley, Peter, 1991 August 13 (Box 5)
    - Cummings, Peter, 1994, undated (Box 5)
    - Cunningham, Brent, 1998, undated; 2 (Box 5)
    - Curnow, Wystan, undated (Box 5)
    - Currey, Richard, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Custer, Chris, 1987-1991, undated; 2 (Box 5)
    - Czerski, Gale, 2006 (Box 5)
    - Dahlen, Beverly, 1987-2006, undated (Box 5)
    - D'Allesandro, Sam, 1984-2006, undated; 6 (Box 5)
    - Dalton, Trinie, 2005 December 08 (Box 5)
    - Daly, Catherine, 2004, undated (Box 5)
    - Daly, Luke, undated (Box 5)
    - Damon, Maria, undated (Box 5)
    - Daniel, Drew, undated (Box 5)
    - Daniels, Gabrielle, undated (Box 5)
    - Darragh, Tina, 1989-2006, undated; 2 (Box 5)
    - Dashiell, David, 1992 (Box 5)
    - David, Don, 1988-1995, undated (Box 5)
    - Davidson, Daniel, 1985-1992, undated; 3 (Box 5)
    - Davidson, Michael, 1994, undated (Box 5)
    - Davies, Alan, 1985-1987, undated (Box 5)
    - Davies, Kevin, 1992 September 10 (Box 5)
    - Davis, Christopher, 1994, undated (Box 5)
    - David, Flora, 1983, undated (Box 5)
    - Davis, Jordan, undated (Box 5)
    - Davis, Leslie, undated (Box 5)
    - Davis, Lydia, 1985-1987, undated (Box 5)
    - Davis, Tim, 2004, undated (Box 5)
    - Davison, Pat, undated (Box 5)
    - Day, Jean, 1987-1993, undated; 2 (Box 5)
    - Day, Ron, 1990-1993, undated; 2 (Box 5)
    - De Angulo, Jaime, undated (Box 5)
    - Deanovich, Connie, 1987-1995, undated; 2 (Box 5)
    - De Beer, Sue, 2005 (Box 5)
    - DeCamp, William, 1987–1989 (Box 5)
    - De Francis, Kathi, 2000 (Box 5)
    - De Graff, Adam, 1995, undated (Box 5)
    - de Gruttola, Raffael, 1996 (Box 5)
    - Delacy, Michael, undated (Box 5)
    - Delany, Samuel R., 1987-1995, undated; 2 (Box 5)
    - de Lissovoy, Noah, 1997, undated (Box 5)
    - Delos, Kate, undated (Box 5)
    - Del Pesco, Joseph, 2008 January 14 (Box 5)
    - De Lynn, Jane, 1990, undated (Box 5)
    - De Silver, Albert, 1998, undated (Box 5)
    - Dougherty, Cecilia, 1998 May 06 (Box 5)
    - Deike, Marta, 1993, undated (Box 5)
    - Denisoff, Denis, 1991-1994, undated; 2 (Box 5)
    - Derkson, Jeff, 1990–1993 (Box 5)
    - De Stefano, Darin, 1991, undated (Box 5)
    - Devaney, Tom, 2004, undated (Box 5)
    - De Vore, Trane, 2000, undated (Box 5)
    - Dewhurst, Robbie, undated (Box 5)
    - Dewitt, Patrick, 2008 December 28 (Box 5)
    - Diamant, Steve, 2004 September 04 (Box 5)
    - Dick, Leslie, 1992, undated (Box 5)
    - Dickinson, Peter, 1997 January 07 (Box 5)
    - Dickison, Steve, 1989-1994, undated (Box 5)
    - Dines, Martin, 2005 August 25 (Box 5)
    - Dienstfrey, Patricia, 2001–2004 (Box 5)
    - Dinshaw, Carolyn, 1994, undated (Box 5)
    - di Prima, Diane, 2004 (Box 5)
    - Di Suvero, Mark, undated (Box 5)
    - Dlugos, Tim, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Doggett, Chris, undated (Box 5)
    - Doherty, Will, 1987, undated (Box 5)
    - Donahue, John, 1984-1987, undated (Box 5)
    - Donnelly, Nisa, undated (Box 5)
    - Donovan, Thom, undated (Box 5)
    - Dorfman, Elsa, 1985, undated (Box 5)
    - Doris, Stacy, undated (Box 5)
    - Dougherty, Cecilia, 1991-2007, undated (Box 6)
    - Downing, Brandon, 2006, undated (Box 6)
    - Downs, Buck, undated (Box 6)
    - Drag Info, 1992, undated (Box 6)
    - Drago, Johnny, undated (Box 6)
    - Dressen, Tiff, undated (Box 6)
    - Drewes, Steffi, 2006, undated (Box 6)
    - Dubowsky, Jack Curtis, 1997, undated (Box 6)
    - Ducharme, Mark, 1993-1996, undated (Box 6)
    - Dunagan, Patrick James, 2005, undated (Box 6)
    - Duncan, Aja Couchois, undated (Box 6)
    - Duncan, Robert, undated (Box 6)
    - Dunn, Carolyn, 2014 (Box 6)
    - DuPlessis, Rachel Blau, 1985-1993, undated (Box 6)
    - Durbin, Andrew, undated (Box 6)
    - Durgin, Patrick, 1998, undated (Box 6)
    - Durrance, Miles, 2005, undated (Box 6)
    - Dye-Giraud, Eric, 1998 April 22 (Box 6)
    - Ebenkamp, Paul, 2013 (Box 6)
    - Eckard, David, 1998, undated (Box 6)
    - Edwards, Kari, 2000 January 02 (Box 6)
    - Edwards, Ken, 1994 June 13 (Box 6)
    - Eigner, Larry, 1995, undated (Box 6)
    - Einzig, Barbara, 1985-1989, undated (Box 6)
    - Eisenman, Nicole, undated (Box 6)
    - El Kholti, Hedi, undated (Box 6)
    - Ellingham, Lew, 1983-2005, undated; 4 (Box 6)
    - Elliott, Anne, 1983 March 14 (Box 6)
    - Ellis, Laura, 2003 January 13 (Box 6)
    - Elmslie, Kenward, 1990-2002, undated (Box 6)
    - Elvovich, Richard, 1988 September 22 (Box 6)
    - Epstein, Andrew, undated (Box 6)
    - Equi, Elaine, 1987–2000 (Box 6)
    - Eros and Writing, 1991, undated (Box 6)
    - Erzen, Tanya, undated (Box 6)
    - Erickson, Steve, 1992 (Box 6)
    - Escoffier, Jeff, 1989-1991, undated (Box 6)
    - Eshleman, Clayton, 1998-1999, undated (Box 6)
    - Essoe, Jordan, undated (Box 6)
    - Estrin, Jerry, 1988-1992, undated (Box 6)
    - Evans, Curtis, undated (Box 6)
    - Evans, George, 1988 December 02 (Box 6)
    - Evans, Simon, undated (Box 6)
    - Evans, Steve, 1997 December 31 (Box 6)
    - Evans, Thomas, 1995, undated (Box 6)
    - Everson, Landis, 2004, undated (Box 6)
    - Ewert, Mark, 1990-1993, undated; 3 (Box 6)
    - Ezawa, Kota, 1997-2010, undated (Box 6)
    - Ezawa, Zora, undated (Box 6)
    - Fabian, Gerald, 1991-03, undated (Box 6)
    - Facchine, Antonio, 1997 October 09 (Box 6)
    - Farmer, Steven, 1996, undated (Box 6)
    - Farrell, Dan, 1996-1999, undated (Box 6)
    - Farwell, David, undated (Box 6)
    - Fattal, Simone, 1997, undated (Box 6)
    - Fazzolari, Bruno, undated (Box 6)
    - Featherston, Dan, 2006 June 06 (Box 6)
    - Fecteau, Vincent, 1995-1997, undated (Box 6)
    - Felix, Joel, undated (Box 6)
    - Felstiner, John, 1998 October 27 (Box 7)
    - Ferguson, Deanna, 1994-1995, undated (Box 7)
    - Fernansez, Vince, 1996 (Box 7)
    - Ferrini, Vincent, 1988-1989, undated (Box 7)
    - Ferro, Robert, 1988 September (Box 7)
    - Field, Edward, undated (Box 7)
    - Field, Sally, 1988 (Box 7)
    - Fishman, Lucy, 2006-2007, undated (Box 7)
    - Fitterman, Rob, 1997-1998, undated (Box 7)
    - Fitzgerald, Dora, 1985, undated (Box 7)
    - Flanagan, Bob, undated (Box 7)
    - Flesh, Henry, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Fodaski, Liz, 1995-1996, undated (Box 7)
    - Ford, Charles Henri, 1991-1997, undated (Box 7)
    - Ford, Michael Thomas, 1995, undated (Box 7)
    - Forrest-Thomson, Veronica, undated (Box 7)
    - Forth, Steven, 1991, undated (Box 7)
    - Fortin, Janice, 1973-1974, undated (Box 7)
    - Foster, Ed, 1988-1995, undated; 2 (Box 7)
    - Foust, Graham, 1996, undated (Box 7)
    - Foye, Raymond, 1973-1991, undated; 4 (Box 7)
    - Fox, Skip, undated (Box 7)
    - Franco, Michael, 1992-1994, undated; 2 (Box 7)
    - Frank, Thaisa, 1985 (Box 7)
    - Fraser, Kathleen, 1985-1997, undated (Box 7)
    - Freeman, Lisa, 2004, undated (Box 7)
    - Freeman, Sharon, 1992 November 12 (Box 7)
    - Friedlander, Ben, 1986, undated (Box 7)
    - Friedman, Michael, 1988-2004, undated (Box 7)
    - Friedman, Robert, 1989-1992, undated (Box 7)
    - Frischelli, G.E., 1980 March 22 (Box 7)
    - Frost, Eric, undated (Box 7)
    - Frym, Gloria, 1987 February 24 (Box 7)
    - Fuller, Heather, 1997-1999, undated (Box 7)
    - Fuller, William, 1990, undated (Box 7)
    - Gadd, Maxine, 1973, undated (Box 7)
    - Gaffney, Elizabeth, 1978-1990, undated (Box 7)
    - Gaitskill, Mary, undated (Box 7)
    - Gallagher, Ellen, undated (Box 7)
    - Gallagher, Kristen, 2000 November 05 (Box 7)
    - Gallery Paul Anglim, undated (Box 7)
    - Gambone, Philip, 1989-1991, undated (Box 7)
    - Gams, Jon, 1996 (Box 7)
    - Gander, Forrest, 1997 (Box 7)
    - Ganick, Peter, 1987-1988, undated (Box 7)
    - Garcia-Torres, Mario, 2008, undated (Box 7)
    - Gardner, Drew, 1992-1993, undated (Box 7)
    - Gascoyne, David, 1995, undated (Box 7)
    - Geary, Patricia, undated (Box 7)
    - George, Diana, undated (Box 7)
    - Gerstler, Amy, 1985-1992, undated (Box 7)
    - Gevirtz, Susan, 1984-1995, undated (Box 7)
    - Giard, Robert, 1987–1995 (Box 8)
    - Gibson, Scott, 1997-2004, undated (Box 8)
    - Gibson, William, 1989 (Box 8)
    - Gil de Montrero, Martha, undated (Box 8)
    - Gilbert, Alan, 1999–2003 (Box 8)
    - Gilbert, David, 1989–1995 (Box 8)
    - Gilbert, Ed, undated (Box 8)
    - Gildzen, Alex, 1991-1992, undated (Box 8)
    - Gillen, Cecilia, undated (Box 8)
    - Ginsberg, Allen, 1993-1995, undated (Box 8)
    - Gio Black Peter, undated (Box 8)
      2 CDs removed for separate housing. See Box 83.
    - Giovanis, Photios, undated (Box 8)
    - Gizzi, Michael, 1994-1996, undated (Box 8)
    - Gizzi, Peter, 1991-2014, undated; 2 (Box 8)
    - Gladman, Renee, 1995, undated (Box 8)
    - Gladstone Gallery, undated (Box 8)
    - Gladstone, Jim, 1997, undated (Box 8)